Contact

nicolereina2009@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nicole-reina-bsn-rn-cen-b173b28b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Registered Nurses

Urgent Care

Certifications

Healthcare Provider CPR/AED

ACLS, PALS, BLS

ENPC- Emergency Nurse Pediatric

Certified

Registered Nurse-RN

CEN- Board Certified Emergency

Nurse

Honors-Awards

Winning Team 1st Annual Nurse Hackathon

Nicole Reina BSN RN CEN

BSN, RN, CEN

Greater New York City Area

Summary

##Nurse 20+ Years / 6 States in \$# BSN RN CEN, MSN, ANP, FNP Student #NursePractitioner ♥## Wife/Mom of 4 Kids, 4 Dogs & 2 Cats ♥## Run, Cook, Crafty

Twitter: @Whatsyourcause

Instagram: NICOLEREINARN

Facebook: Nicole Reina

Pinterest: Nicole Reina BSN RN CEN

Experience

Newton Urgent Care Registered Nurse May 2014 - Present (6 years 1 month)

Newton, New Jersey

Stabilize and care of urgent and emergent patients across the lifespan.

HireNurses.com
VP Social Media & Community Engagement
January 2017 - Present (3 years 5 months)

Boston, Massachusetts

Hirenurses is a nationally recognized leader in Nurse Advocacy, Education & Talent Management created by Nurses for Nurses. We have National and International career opportunities and development, along with medical mission trips for Nurse Practitioners and Nurses.

Sparta Board Of Education RN, Substitute School Nurse March 2015 - Present (5 years 3 months)

Bogota High School
Team Nurse-JV Football Team
September 2014 - Present (5 years 9 months)
New Jersey

Team Nurse for JV High School Team each Fall. Provide care to injured players & Injury Prevention

Registered Nurse 2000 - Present (20 years)

Carolinas Healthcare System RN- Emergency Department 2012 - 2013 (1 year)

Emergency Department RN, Regional Chest Pain Center, Stroke Center

Atlantic Health System 8 years

RN- Emergency Department 2004 - 2012 (8 years) Greater New York City Area

Emergency Department RN, Triage Nurse, Psych Emergency Services RN, State Designated Stroke Center

RN- Cardiac Transport Team Nurse 2004 - 2005 (1 year)

Critical Care Transport- Transported Critical Cardiac Catheratization patients from outlying regional facilities to World Renouned Cardiac Cath Lab and Open Heart/Cardio-Thorasic Surgical Hospital and Center.

Tenet Healthcare

RN- Critical and Intensive Care, Emergency Department Nurse 2001 - 2003 (2 years)

Delray Beach, FL

Critical Care Float Pool- CCU, TICU/PTICU, ER, SICU, MICU, CVICU, Neuro ICU

American Traveler Staffing Professionals RN- Critical and Intensive Care Nurse 2000 - 2001 (1 year) Clearwater, FL

Contract Travel Nurse specializing in Critical Care

Licensed Practical Nurse LPN Licensed Practical Nurse August 1997 - May 2000 (2 years 10 months) New Jersey, Virginia

LPN

Licensed Practical Nurse May 1997 - May 2000 (3 years 1 month)

Inova Health System
LPN, Critical and Intensive Care Nurse
1998 - 2000 (2 years)
CCU, Critical Care Stepdown

George Mason University Higher Education School Nurse 1997 - 2000 (3 years)

Student Health Services, Community Health and Wellness Education

Supervised BSN student nurses in full service Student Health Clinic,
Organized and Co-Chaired University wide Community Health and Fitness
Fair, Ran Flu Shot Clinic, Immunization Clinic- both National and International
Travelers Program, Set up Health Education Programing for GMU Fairfax, Va
Campus

Education

George Mason University

Bachelor's Degree in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (1997 - 2000)

INOVA Juniper Program/ PA/ Mid Atlantic AIDS Education and Training Center

Certificate, HIV/ AIDS Clinical Training Program · (1999)

Sussex County Technical School
LPN- Licensed Practical Nurse, Nursing (1996 - 1997)

Sussex County Community College

EMT; Night & Summer Classes in HS (High School), Emergency Medical Technology/Technician (EMT B) · (1994 - 1996)